boys we are going to talk about quickly
the five steps i would take to become a
full-time trader i've done it and this
is what i think would be the best
approach most realistic and the safest
because we don't want to become homeless
let's dive into it
[Music]
so the number one most important thing
you need to start doing very first step
of course we're gonna have to get some
sort of education the first one is
education and this is going to encompass
working as with a team of other people
so you're gonna have to find either
mentors online or chat rooms where you
can bounce ideas off of people don't
just watch youtube but youtube is the
starting point that's where i would
start that being said youtube is a
horrible place to learn strategies that
actually work but you can get logic
there that's what i really suggest a lot
of my stuff is going to have logic in it
the strategies themselves they suck but
you can play off of the strategies to
make working things for yourself use
those ideas to then build off of it the
whole point of this education phase is
to make ideas that you can then build a
strategy based off of from the education
right
second step is we are going to be doing
testing you have to obviously find very
simple rules for you to follow so that
when you're back testing you're able to
focus on each variable so that you can
then find which
of these ideas are actually making
profit how much profit they are making
and you really want to make sure that
they're actually making significant
profit because when you do come to live
testing phase you're going to [__] up a
lot so then you're going to dive into
live testing and what this is going to
be doing is after you've found something
that works on a back test let's say
it works profitably after 25 tests then
you can start live testing what i
suggest doing this to is a three month
continuous basis for your trading every
day and if you're able to make money
three months in a row then we're gonna
say okay that's a good strategy keep
doing that and don't [__] with it okay
don't [__] with the strategy don't try
to learn new strategies and add [__] to
it keep that for a while before you
start adding more after you're done
live testing and you've been trading
that method for a while you can see keep
tracking uh different variables uh to
see how you can make it slightly
slightly better but you have to be very
careful with this that you don't get
some sort of strategy slip and then you
start doing a strategy that's no longer
the actual working strategy that you
originally found to be very careful
about going through that
number three that would actually be
smarter to do as number two is i would
get some sort of side income and i
wouldn't honestly be working
an actual job if this is what you for
sure want to do i would not be working a
full-time job i would do a part-time job
something you can do on the side side
hustle that you can already make a
little bit of money so that you have
full control over when you're working i
did something similar with this uh with
youtube i made the youtube channel and
then as i was trading in my early-ish
days of trading where i was you know i
knew what i was doing i just wasn't good
at it yet then i was starting to make
money on the youtube and then i could
quit my job no yeah you're not
everything's fine hey listen i quit once
you want to quit your job you need some
sort of side income so this is why it's
kind of a two-three overlap type thing
and i'm not going to tell you what to do
for your side hustle some sort of way to
make money on the side that's it you
would need to not be focused on the
trading earnings when you're early into
this because you are going to lose money
if you have to make money
the fourth one uh would be to get funded
somehow this can mean either doing a
funded trader challenge or investing in
some sort of thing like crypto where
you're able to get a lot of money so
this is where you're gonna have to build
up a large amount of capital because
trading in itself is very slow process
for building large capital but it will
make a lot of money once you do have
that large capital again uh this is
general rule of thumb you're gonna need
money somehow
and then the fifth thing guys this is
what i really suggest is once you are
making money good money with trading
don't live off of it put it somewhere
else where you're gonna make passive
income because again this is a video all
about how are we gonna make that money
from trading and then live off of it in
longevity wise right so if something
does go wrong your method suddenly
doesn't work anymore or markets are
crashing something like this and you're
not making money anymore you need to
live so i personally don't live off of
any of my trading income don't live off
of my investment income i don't live off
my trading income i then take all those
profits and put it in passive income
sources where i'm now living off the
passive income sources you know things
like this would be example real estate
an atm business do dividends laundry map
machines who cares [__] it doesn't
matter some way to make passive income
uh and then just live off of that and
that's it guys so uh number one get some
[__] knowledge number two um
what's number two
testing
uh
test that knowledge number three get
some side income so that when you're
actually trading you're not [__] up
and uh number four get big money somehow
from not trading and then don't live off
the money
easy enough guys see you next time
[Music]
oh